AHMAD

SAHRO



Contact

Address:

Komando III Street, Number 25 Setia Budi South Jakarta.

Phone:

+628 - 190 - 605 - 8312

Email:

contact@ahmadsahro.website

Languages

English

Indonesia

Summary

I was a student of D3 ITB from 2013 to 2016. After graduated I work as full stack php programer. I was create an web base aplication using any frame work like codeigniter and laravel from I was collage student until now. The applicatication like online shop, recruitment system, company profile, and else, I has created in this 5 years.

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused

Experience

Internet Marketing - 2016 to 2017

PT Alexindo Putra Mandiri, West jakarta

I worked as an Internet Marketing with tasks such as creating websites, SEO, Google ads, Facebook ads, and several other tasks in the IT field.

Junior Web Developer - 2018 to 2019

PT Cartenz Teknologi Indonesia, South Jakarta

I worked as an Junior Web Programing with tasks to Create web base application that customer request such as Portal Information, Document Aplyment, Recruitment, and Notify.

Web Developer - 2019 to Now

Luna Web Design, Central Jakarta

I worked as an Web Programing with tasks to maintenance and update feature of metube.id and the cms. The website look like youtube and builded using vue js and golang.

Education

Diploma of Enginering: **Metrology and Intrumentation** - 2013 **Bandung Intitute of Technology (ITB)**, Bandung

Bachelor of Enginering: **Phisyc Enginering** - 2017 **Nasional University (Unas)**, Jakarta